export const QuizData = {
    questions: [
        {
            question: 'What movie did Thanos first appear in?',
            answer1: 'Avengers',
            answer2: 'Thor',
            answer3: 'Thor: The Dark World',
            answer4: 'Captain America: Civil War',
            correctAnswer: 'answer1',
            key: "1A"
        },
        {
            question: 'What was the Space Stone originally called?',
            answer1: 'The Portal Generator',
            answer2: 'The Blue Source',
            answer3: 'The Tesseract',
            answer4: 'The Ultimate Weapon',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: "1B"
        },
        {
            question: 'Which ex-Avenger is now leading a fugitive team?',
            answer1: 'Iron Man',
            answer2: 'Ant Man',
            answer3: 'Falcon',
            answer4: 'Captain America',
            correctAnswer: 'answer4',
            key: "1C"
        },
        {
            question: "Which member of Iron Man's Civil War team went 'rogue'?",
            answer1: 'Scarlet Witch',
            answer2: 'Black Widow',
            answer3: 'Vision',
            answer4: 'Black Panther',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: "1D"
        },
        {
            question: "What is the name of Thanos's gang of sidekicks?",
            answer1: 'The Black Order',
            answer2: 'Tha Dark Marks',
            answer3: 'The Shadow Children',
            answer4: 'The Killer Maw',
            correctAnswer: 'answer1',
            key: "1E"
        },
        {
            question: 'How is Thanos combining the Infinity Stones?',
            answer1: 'Glove of Power',
            answer2: 'Infinity Glove',
            answer3: 'Gauntlet of Power',
            answer4: 'Infinity Gauntlet',
            correctAnswer: 'answer4',
            key: "1F"
        },
        {
            question: 'Who stole the Power Stone?',
            answer1: 'Drax the Destroyer',
            answer2: 'ronan the Accuser',
            answer3: 'Star-Lord',
            answer4: 'Rocket Racoon',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: "1G"
        },
        {
            question: "What is the name of Black Panther's home?",
            answer1: "K'un Lun",
            answer2: 'Wakanda',
            answer3: 'Kamar Taj',
            answer4: 'Khokarsa',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: "1H"
        },
        {
            question: 'Which film does the Reality Stone first appear in?',
            answer1: 'Captain America: Civil War',
            answer2: 'Guardians of the Galaxy',
            answer3: 'Black Panther',
            answer4: 'Thor: The Dark World',
            correctAnswer: 'answer4',
            key: "1I"
        },
        {
            question: 'How did Thor lose his eye?',
            answer1: 'Fighting Hela',
            answer2: 'Fighting Thanos',
            answer3: 'Fighting Loki',
            answer4: 'Fighting Hulk',
            correctAnswer: 'answer1',
            key: "1J"
        },
        {
            question: 'Which planet was Thanos born on?',
            answer1: 'Mogo',
            answer2: 'Xander',
            answer3: 'Titan',
            answer4: 'BattleWorld',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: "1K"
        },
        {
            question: 'Which android did Tony Stark create (that tried to kill everyone)?',
            answer1: 'JARVIS',
            answer2: 'FRIDAY',
            answer3: 'ULTRON',
            answer4: 'VISION',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: "1L"
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the name of the pendant that houses the Time Stone?',
            answer1: 'The Immortal Eye',
            answer2: 'The Eye of Agamotto',
            answer3: 'The Pendant of Time',
            answer4: 'The Great Green Eye',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: "1M"
        },
        {
            question: 'Who cameos in every Marvel movie?',
            answer1: 'Kevin Fridge',
            answer2: 'Jack Kirby',
            answer3: 'Joss Whedon',
            answer4: 'Stan Lee',
            correctAnswer: 'answer4',
            key: "1N"
        },
        {
            question: 'When did Thanos first appear in a post-credits scene?',
            answer1: 'Doctor Stange',
            answer2: 'Avengers: The age of Ultron',
            answer3: 'The Avengers',
            answer4: 'Guardians of the Galaxy',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: "1O"
        },
        {
            question: 'How did Dr Strange defeat Dormammu?',
            answer1: 'Building an Energy Prison',
            answer2: 'Creating a Time Loop',
            answer3: 'Foze Time',
            answer4: 'Fast Forwarded Time Past for his Life',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: "1P"
        },
        {
            question: "Who killed Tony Stark's parents?",
            answer1: 'Bucky Barnes',
            answer2: 'Sam Wilson',
            answer3: 'Black Widow',
            answer4: 'War Machiene',
            correctAnswer: 'answer1',
            key: "1Q"
        },
        {
            question: "Who is the trainer of Doctor Strange?",
            answer1: "The Ancient One",
            answer2: 'Wong',
            answer3: 'Pang born',
            answer4: 'Doctor Palmer',
            correctAnswer: 'answer1',
            key: "1R"
        },
        {
            question: "Who is the avenger who sacrificed his/her life for earning the soul stone?",
            answer1: "The Ancient One",
            answer2: 'Black Widow',
            answer3: 'Hawk Eye',
            answer4: 'Iron Man',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: "1S"
        },
        {
            question: "'You cut-off one head two will take its place' is the famous slogan of which group",
            answer1: 'Wakandian Group',
            answer2: 'Hydra Group',
            answer3: 'Fugitive Group',
            answer4: 'Antonion Group',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: "1T"
        },
    ]
}